auctelia.com 2013-02-12

# Auctelia

At the company Auctelia SA (hereafter called "Auctelia") we are strongly committed to preserving the privacy of our Users’ personal data. This Privacy Policy provides an explanation as to how Auctelia uses any of the personal information provided to us by our Users or collected by us through our websites www.auctelia.com, www.auctelia.be and www.auctelia.eu (hereafter called the “Website”). Any violation whatsoever of the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy may result in the suspension of the offending User’s access privileges. 

Auctelia complies with the Belgian law of December 8th 1992 relating to the protection of privacy. This law stipulates that the person or company collecting personal data must secure the prior consent of the person whose personal details are involved; the data must be relevant to the purpose for which it is collected as well as not excessive in relation to the purpose of processing; the data must be accurate; the data must be collected to a specific, clear and lawful purpose. Persons whose personal data have been collected are allowed access to the information held about them and may amend the information contained therein. 

#### Why do we collect your personal information?

Auctelia collects and processes the data pertaining to visitors to and Users of the Website, in order to achieve the company’s objects, improve the Website, improve the products and services on offer, and establish statistical data about our Users. The information that you provide us can be used to allow us to contact you if necessary but also enables us to keep you informed of the Website’s newest features. This information can also be used to offer you products and services which we believe may be of interest to you, except if you expressly notify us that you do not wish to receive such information. Under no circumstances whatsoever will your personal data be communicated, disclosed or forwarded to third parties. 

#### What kind of information do we collect? 

When you visit our Website, Auctelia can collect personal information about you by directly requesting it from you (such as on a registration form) or we can collect non-personal information in an indirect manner, by tracking your use of the Website. We collect and use the following information: 

  * All of the information pertaining to the pages visited by the User; 
  * All of the mandatory personal information provided when registering on the Website (such as name, address, landline number, mobile phone number, e-mail); 
  * The websites that you visited before and after using our website; 
  * The length of your visit to our Website.

#### Cookies

All this information is collected with the help of a “cookie”. A cookie is a small alphanumeric identifier that our Web server stores on your computer’s hard drive. We use cookies to make our Website easier to use and faster to access, for example by saving your language preference. You can either enable or disable cookies by modifying your browser’s settings. 

#### Third party websites

You might find links to third party websites on our Website. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to these third party websites. We have no control over their privacy policies. Auctelia does not accept any liability or responsibility whatsoever for the content of these third party websites and/or the business practices of the owners or network operators of these third party websites. 

#### Rights

At any time you may inform us whether or not you want to receive marketing emails from Auctelia via your account settings. 

#### Contact us

We welcome any questions you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or the processing of your personal data. Please do not hesitate to contact us at info@auctelia.com or by mail: 

Auctelia SA   
Avenue des Métallurgistes 22B   
B-1490 Court-Saint-Etienne, Belgium   

#### Changes in our Privacy Policy

Auctelia reserves the right to amend or update the terms of this Privacy Policy from time to time. The amendments are effective as soon as they are published on the Website. Auctelia suggests that our Users frequently check our Privacy Policy so that they are informed of any possible changes. 

###### By your continued use of this Website you will be deemed to have accepted the terms and conditions detailed in this Privacy Policy. We will also make the assumption that you consent to providing Auctelia with personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Furthermore, you will be deemed to consent to Auctelia’s use and processing of your personal data. 

Copyright © 2009-2013 Auctelia SA
